<problem display_name="Quiz: Dana's Designs" markdown="Dana took a look at David's conceptual challenges and needs and worked with him to identify the design requirements to address his concerns.  The previous demo shows how easy TAPS is to run.  The Work-In-Progress extended abstract discusses the design challenges in more detail.&#10;&#10;&#10;&gt;&gt;Which of the following design challenges did Dana identify and solve to address David's conceptual challenges?&lt;&lt;&#10;&#10;[ ] Creating a userID   {{ U: -- Right! This is easy to do on the MOSS website. }, { S: -- Anyone can get a userID from the MOSS website.}}&#10;[x] Mixed Languages  {{ selected: -- Correct! Instructors must review the suspicious similarities highlighted by MOSS to determine plagiarism. Comparisons of students against their own previous projects or past semester similarities already reviewed, for example, will produce false positives that overshadow the current project analysis.  These need to be filtered out. }, { unselected: -- If not filtered out, false positives can overshadow true positives. }}&#10;[x] File Management {{ selected: -- Correct! Tedious tasks such as unzipping submissions and flattening nested folders are automated in TAPS}, { unselected: -- automating tedious tasks is what tools do best. }}&#10;[x] Filtering {{ selected: -- Correct! A couple of David's challenges involved filtering unwanted information out of the analysis}, { unselected: -- Unwanted pairing of past submissions against each other and false positives overshadow useful information}}&#10;[x] Cross-platform  {{ selected: -- Correct! Using pure Java makes the solution more general as it can be used on multiple platforms. }, { unselected: -- MOSS is provided with a UNIX script and not guaranteed to work on other platforms.}}&#10;[ ] Clustering results   {{ U: -- Right!  TAPS is a Work-In-Progress and doesn't include this feature, which might be a way to identify rings of plagiarism}, { S: -- This might be a great feature, but it's not implemented in the current TAPS Work-In-Progress version}}&#10;&#10;&#10;&#10;||In the video, Dana identified four design challenges to solve.||&#10;||The challenges Dana identified are related to scaling, filtering, and usability for the tool. ||&#10;">
<p>Dana took a look at David's conceptual challenges and needs and worked with him to identify the design requirements to address his concerns.  The previous demo shows how easy TAPS is to run.  The Work-In-Progress extended abstract discusses the design challenges in more detail.</p>
<p>Which of the following design challenges did Dana identify and solve to address David's conceptual challenges?</p>
<choiceresponse>
  <checkboxgroup label="Which of the following design challenges did Dana identify and solve to address David's conceptual challenges?">
    <choice correct="false">Creating a userID
      <choicehint selected="true">-- Anyone can get a userID from the MOSS website.</choicehint>
      <choicehint selected="false">-- Right! This is easy to do on the MOSS website.</choicehint></choice>
    <choice correct="true">Mixed Languages
      <choicehint selected="true">-- Correct! Instructors must review the suspicious similarities highlighted by MOSS to determine plagiarism. Comparisons of students against their own previous projects or past semester similarities already reviewed, for example, will produce false positives that overshadow the current project analysis.  These need to be filtered out.</choicehint>
      <choicehint selected="false">-- If not filtered out, false positives can overshadow true positives.</choicehint></choice>
    <choice correct="true">File Management
      <choicehint selected="true">-- Correct! Tedious tasks such as unzipping submissions and flattening nested folders are automated in TAPS</choicehint>
      <choicehint selected="false">-- automating tedious tasks is what tools do best.</choicehint></choice>
    <choice correct="true">Filtering
      <choicehint selected="true">-- Correct! A couple of David's challenges involved filtering unwanted information out of the analysis</choicehint>
      <choicehint selected="false">-- Unwanted pairing of past submissions against each other and false positives overshadow useful information</choicehint></choice>
    <choice correct="true">Cross-platform
      <choicehint selected="true">-- Correct! Using pure Java makes the solution more general as it can be used on multiple platforms.</choicehint>
      <choicehint selected="false">-- MOSS is provided with a UNIX script and not guaranteed to work on other platforms.</choicehint></choice>
    <choice correct="false">Clustering results
      <choicehint selected="true">-- This might be a great feature, but it's not implemented in the current TAPS Work-In-Progress version</choicehint>
      <choicehint selected="false">-- Right!  TAPS is a Work-In-Progress and doesn't include this feature, which might be a way to identify rings of plagiarism</choicehint></choice>
  </checkboxgroup>
</choiceresponse>


<demandhint>
  <hint>In the video, Dana identified four design challenges to solve.</hint>
  <hint>The challenges Dana identified are related to scaling, filtering, and usability for the tool.</hint>
</demandhint>
</problem>
