<annotatable display_name="Definitions and Assumptions">
<p id="quote">"(...) we can never assume that the impact of teaching on student learning is what we expect it to be. Students’ thoughts and actions are profoundly affected by the educational context or environment in which they learn. (...) Good teaching involves striving continually to learn about students’ understanding and the effect of teaching on it"</p>
<p align="right"><span id="author"><a href="#nine">Paul Ramsden, 1992 p6</a></span></p>

<p>Taking a student-centred approach, Barnett, indicated that the process of studying and learning at University is not only about the acquisition of theoretical knowledge and transferable skills, but it is also intertwined with issues of personal growth and social development, both of which could have a positive influence on either their academic training or experience [<a href="#ten">10</a>]. </p>
<p>However, particularly in a climate in which university fees are becoming a long-term investment/debt that many students have to weight up, it is no surprise that a <em>consumer-type</em> perspective has gained greater importance. This partly explains the resurgence of research on the evaluation of teaching in the literature in HE as one of the key factors affecting students"experiences.</p>

<p>Baird and Gordon [<a href="#eleven">11</a>] suggested six possible perspectives on Student Experience.</p>

<ul>
	<li>"<em><annotation title="Please comment on:" body="The total student experience" highlight="blue" problem="0">All life experiences of all students while they are students".</annotation></em> This is similar to Harveys et al. [<a href="#twelve">12</a>] reference to the "total student experience".</li>
	<li>"<em><annotation title="Please comment on:" body="The total student experience" highlight="yellow" problem="1">All experiences of an individual while a student, which includes wider life experiences"</annotation></em>. This is akin to the conceptualisation of Krause et al. [<a href="#fourteen">15</a>] who included in their experience survey questions specifically related to expectations, adjustment and engagement.</li>
	<li>"<em><annotation title="Please comment on:" body="Experience while in a student role" highlight="blue" problem="2">All experiences of an individual student while in their identity as student"</annotation></em>; this is similar to Pate [<a href="#fourteen">14</a>], but for the institutions such a position lends itself to a disaggregation along a student lifecycle, which allows to probe students at different stages (i.e. the first year experience, the postgraduate experience etc).</li>
	<li>A fourth definition, focuses on the <annotation title="Please comment on:" body="Facets of experience" highlight="yellow" problem="3">facets of university experienced by a student</annotation> and therefore the focus is specifically on a clear sense of belonging to the institution.</li>
	<li>A fifth perspective is <annotation title="Please comment on:" body="The student experience as consumer" highlight="blue" problem="4">the "consumer" </annotation>one in which aspects of the services provided are considered (for example administrative procedures, catering, accommodation, IT etc). This is the traditional view of the <em>marketer</em> as it allows the body of students to be treated as consumers with different needs and expectations, which give management the opportunity to tailor the services provided and cater for these perceived needs.</li>
	<li>Another one encompassing "<em><annotation title="Please comment on:" body="The student personal development" highlight="yellow" problem="5">all experiences which contribute to one"s personal development as learner</annotation>" </em>(in this sense also termed the student learning experience). The latter is more specific and there is a strong implicit assumption about the role fulfilled by HE programmes.</li>
</ul>

<p>All these have in common the assumption that the student experience is something that can be identified as a holistic or universal concept, but Radloff and colleagues argue that</p>
<p id="quote"> "<em>Student experience(s)</em> are unique for each individual, across the range of contexts through which students engage as part of their university studies: there is no such thing as <em>the </em>student experience."(Radloff et al 2011:35)</p>

<p>In fact, even for students registered in different degree programmes within the same institution, it is common that students come across completely different patterns of teaching and assessment that determine the nature of their interactions and perception of the respective environments.</p>

<p>Baird and Gordon [<a href="#eleven">11</a>] suggested that to get beyond perspectives on the student experience and to productively examine what <em>student experience</em> means, one needs to consider the common goals characterising all students deciding to enrol on a university course at a particular institution. They list three:</p>
 <ul>
<li>personal development and transformation through learning;
</li>
<li>direct future benefits in terms of employability, social standing and contributions to society and communities;   </li>
<li>a match or ‘fit’ between the student and the university in terms of areas of study or institutional/ departmental culture.</li> 
  </ul>
</annotatable>
