<annotatable display_name="Technology Issues">

<p id="quote">"<strong><annotation title="Please comment on:" body="The pedagogy in the MOOCs" highlight="blue" problem="0">MOOCs make little of established best practices in online pedagogy</annotation></strong>. Online education has come a long way, with programs reflecting commendable strides in pedagogy, student mentoring, outcomes measurement, inquiry-based learning models, and effectiveness in the use of collaborative learning tools. MOOCs, on the other hand, are shockingly austere, relying heavily on lectures, multiple choice exams, and threaded discussions with little sustained faculty involvement or guidance for learning."</p>
<p align="right"><span id="author"><a href="http://www.eduventures.com/2013/04/learning-from-moocs-unmasking-the-weaknesses-of-online-education/" target="_blank">Brian Fleming, 2013 </a></span></p>

<p>In an <a href="https://www.insidehighered.com/views/2013/04/25/moocs-do-not-represent-best-online-learning-essay" target="_blank">interesting essay about MOOCs</a> and their development, Legon argues that the first generation of MOOCs does not represent best online pedagogy and it is surprising that they received so much attention simply based on the fact that"</p>
<p id="quote">"With Stanford and Harvard professors leading the way, the assumption seems to be that those at the top of the educational pyramid would not only deliver the best content, but also know best how to teach more effectively online than do faculty and staff at lesser institutions. <br/>
This assumed connection between content expertise and a mature grasp of the challenges of online teaching, however, has not been demonstrated in MOOCs."</p>
<p align="right"><span id="author"><a href="https://www.insidehighered.com/views/2013/04/25/moocs-do-not-represent-best-online-learning-essay" target="_blank">Ronal Legon, 2013 </a></span></p>

<p>With MOOC platform providers maturing very quickly, experimenting constantly and often guided by a compromise between a development roadmap and institutional partners' demands, it is not surprising that to leverage on opportunities, the courses delivered have to adaptive.</p>

<p>This has been the case for all the MOOCs developed by UNSW Australia. If on one side this forced the design teams to experiment with the features and capabilities, this has not always resulted in an improvement, which will become evident from the data presented.</p>

<p/>

</annotatable>
