<annotatable display_name="Problems with the 'student' experience">
<p>In a seminal work on student experience in higher education, Pascarella " Terenzini explored the variety of aspects that affect student experience [<a href="#five">5</a>]. <strong>Some</strong> of these are directly related to learning and teaching, others have to do with the life beyond class. <strong>All</strong> of these affect the way students experience learning and influence their level of satisfaction. </p>

<p><annotation title="Discuss student experience" body="Is this really problematic?" highlight="yellow" problem="0">However, the concept of <strong><em>student experience</em></strong> is problematic. </annotation> <br/>Despite being discussed as a notion since the 30s by Dewey [<a href="#five">6</a>], the formal reference to student experience received a new thrust relatively recently and the focus is a more holistic representation of what it means for a student to be a student and the experience associated with earning a university qualification.</p>
<p> The idea that being at university is not only limited to teaching and it is not just about transmitting or receiving information are straightforward. It is also a fact that students are paying larger fees, while their experience of education in a rapidly changing environment. The massification of the HE sector (i.e. large increase in student numbers, lowering of entry level/grades, internationalization, blended and distance education) also contributed to the change of focus to considering students like consumers, and as a result, triggered the need to extend the collection of feedback beyond the satisfaction with teaching. </p>

<p>Firstly, the idea of <em>student</em> in a MOOC in the tranditional sense present major issues:</p>
<ul>
<li>participants (in most cases) do not pay to enrol</li>
<li>participants might not intend to follow the MOOC from start to finish</li>
<li>participants may not want to complete assessment</li>
<li>there are many assumptions about the target audience and level of the material</li>
</ul>
<p>Secondly, defining the idea of experience presents some difficulty as the terms used to refer to the experience in the literature are far from clear.</p>
<p>In the short survey at the beginning of the paper we asked you to define for key terms: 1) student <em>experience</em>; 2) student <em>engagement</em>; 3) student <em>satisfaction</em>; and 4) student <em>evaluation of teaching</em>.</p>

<p>Following the link you will be able to see a live submission of the results [link to results here]</p>
<h5>References</h5>
<div id="references">
<p><a name="five">[5]</a> E. T. Pascarella, <em>How college affects students</em>. San Francisco, Calif: Jossey-Bass, 2005.<br/>
<a name="five">[6] </a> J. Dewey. <em>Education and experience.</em> New York: Macmillan, 1938. </p>
</div>
</annotatable>
